plotdog.com 2016-04-01

# Privacy - Plotdog

Your personal information is under our protection. Assuming you want to give it to us to begin with.

You see, here at Plotdog we believe in your right to control your personal information. If we ask you for your name, email address, phone number, or any other type of information that can be used to identify you as an individual (for the purpose of contacting you to answer a question or hook you up with additional material or similar communication), you can be assured that we keep that information secure in our network. Plotdog does not share or sell your information to third party organizations.

You also have the right to ask us to update our records with new information about you, or remove it altogether.

[Plotdog](http://plotdog.com/ "Plotdog") does collect a variety of other information through the use of log files and browser cookies and similar tracking methods. These are tools we use on the website to know how many unique IP addresses visit our site, which pages they visit, how often, and so on. Analyzing our traffic data is how we discern what improvements to make to the site and when. This type of information, such as IP addresses, ISP, and browser, cannot be used to personally identify you. Your personal information must be collected separately.

However, you may choose to turn off cookies using your own browser settings on your computer. Please keep in mind that if you disable the use of cookies on your computer, you may not be able to see or use all parts of the Plotdog website.

If you follow an outgoing link on our site and navigate off this site, our privacy policy will no longer apply to that third party website. Please locate and read the privacy policy of any site you visit by clicking an outgoing link, to ensure that you are aware of how your information is being tracked and used there.
